{
    "id": "cb65f29c18ec412a80de2e5b2a8a2625",
    "title": "Primary Auxiliary Verbs Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "…………………….. you have a car?",
            "description": "Use do with you. In the simple present tense, we make questions and negatives with do and does. ",
            "answers": [
                "Is",
                "Are",
                "Do",
                "Does"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "37c9b429e5bd40e9833a2a836161e474"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………………. you doing there?",
            "description": "The present continuous form is made with is/am/are + ing. Use are with you.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "70f7e99a98fa4859a746d0386440ffa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………………. you want?",
            "description": "In the simple present tense, we make questions and negatives with do or does.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "are",
                "do"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7b4f82a2a4f34fb5ae038bc412253714"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………. arrived yet.",
            "description": "The past participle is used with has/have.",
            "answers": [
                "didn't",
                "hasn't",
                "isn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "17cc05c45b764b6ba1eeeb4b67609a4f"
        },
        {
            "question": "It ……………………. stopped raining since yesterday.",
            "description": "The past participle is used with has or have. ",
            "answers": [
                "didn't",
                "isn't",
                "hasn't"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "674f761017134afea65416976d114a71"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………. never helped me with anything.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d047c6886c2b4390ad09b388f6ab71d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ………………………. waiting for them.",
            "description": "Use is/am/are with the ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "492cb9a7fd39466ca395ad11394723cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Why …………………….. you looking at me like that?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94561ea3249a49739d0b27f4396502bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ……………………… you do then?",
            "description": "In the simple past we make questions with did.",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "did",
                "were"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e0a22e99f24e410f8cbe172e7f56cbdd"
        },
        {
            "question": "Whom …………………….. you want to meet?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0f303256c35b4ef1b128180cd64d1810"
        },
        {
            "question": "She said that she ……………………… coming.",
            "description": "When the main verb is in the past tense, the other verbs too should be in the past tense.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "does",
                "was"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "32bb9ffedfcc4bcab5dc8a5c05137120"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………… know who I am.",
            "description": "In the simple present, we make questions and negatives with do and does. ",
            "answers": [
                "didn't",
                "hasn't",
                "doesn't",
                "isn't"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "42b40dc024b9439083e6290d6d31a6cc"
        }
    ]
}